Abdelhameed Ibrahim Hamed Elshershaby

Address: 6th Of October, Egypt Phone: 01228630813

Email:

Abdelhameed.elshershaby@gmail.com

Summary

Senior SAP MM/EWM/VMS Consultant with experience in requirement gathering, system configuration and support. Basic ABAP knowledge, able to create basic custom programs with strong debugging knowledge. Multiple end to end implementations inside and outside of Egypt.

Skill Highlights

- Onboard planning
- Advanced search abilities
- Self motivated

- Problem-solving
- Teamwork
- Analytical thinking

Experience

Almansour Automotive (04/2018 – current)

Sr. SAP MM/EWM/VMS consultant

- Gather and analyze business requirements, design and configure SAP MM/EWM solutions to meet those requirements
- Test and debug SAP MM/EWM configurations to ensure they are functioning correctly
- Train clients on how to use the SAP system, and provide ongoing support as needed
- Work with other SAP modules, such as SAP SD (Sales and Distribution), SAP FICO (Finance and controlling to ensure that the SAP MM system integrates seamlessly with other systems
- Collaborate with other team members, including developers and project managers, to deliver high-quality solutions to clients
- Prepare and develop the user manuals required
- Manage master data preparation & mass uploading (data migration) using SAP standard and customized methods
- Create authorization matrix from scratch
- Analyzed the issues raised by end users and providing support required through multiple ticketing systems
- Create simple ABAP reports and upload programs to facilitate complicated business requirements as mass initial stock upload and invoice upload using excel sheet
- Train new hires and ensure smooth and fast knowledge transfer

- Delta Egypt Company for Processing Labs (June 2017-December 2017)
 Sales representative
- Achieved sales target and ranked top 3 sales representatives for 6 months
- Network Marketing (March 2017-June 2017)

Online sales and customer service

C.G.A.A of Professional Accountants Academy (February 2016-January 2017)

Part-time Accountant Trainee

projects

- Mansour MG Automotive
- MANSCO Peugeot
- MAC Libya
- Mantra motorbikes East Africa-Uganda
- MAC East Africa LTD-Tanzania
- EWM full Implementations (Mansour-Mansco-Mg)

Courses

• Jupiter 2000 (Jan 2018-April 2018)

SAP MM consulting course (80 hours)

• Allied Consultants Company for SAP Services (September 2017-November 2017)

SAP FI consulting course (80 hours, Final Project included)

• Future Learn (may 2017 -august 2017)

Many short courses and technical events

• Training course (February 2016-March 2016)

Financial, Construction and tax Accounting

Education

Bachelor's degree in English Accounting – 2015 Tanta University

Languages

Arabic - Native English – Fluent